Guide to the Alumni Association Records 1888-2008
Oregon State University Libraries, University Archives
- Microfilmed Records, 1888-1964; Subgroup 4
  - Stadium Fund, 1951-1953; Series XV (Reel 4-6)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1953; Series XVI (Reel 6-9)
  - General Files, 1935-1950; Series XVIII (Reel 9-13)
    Series XVIII includes accounting and administrative records; materials pertaining to Association publications (the alumni magazine and Orange and Black; narrative reports; correspondence; and reports regarding controversies between Oregon State College and the University of Oregon.
  - Memorial Chapel and Carillon, 1944-1959; Series XIX (Reel 13)
    Series XIX includes materials pertaining to the proposed memorial chapel and the carillon for the Memorial Union. Correspondence with other universities regarding campus chapels and religious programs is part of this series.